(Raj:)...you've had removed from your body
over the years.
I didn't know you could have
a cyst inside another cyst.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)The doctor said they were like
Russian nesting dolls.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Well, if you have to go, how about
I put a little doggie bag together for you?
(Raj:)That would be lovely, thank you.
(Scene:)Mrs. Wolowitz...
(Raj:)...are you okay?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Don't mind me.
I just cry when I'm Ionely
and have nothing to live for.
(Leonard:)I...
(Raj:)I suppose I could stay for some dessert.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Great. You like
chocolate chip cheesecake?
(Howard:)- Sure.
- I'll make one.
(Sheldon:)One vintage Mr. Mxyzptlk action figure.
(Sheldon:)- That's Leonard's.
- Children's toy.
One Star Trek: The Next Generation
phaser.